Guide to the C. Harrison Mann, Jr. papers, 1950-1977
George Mason University Libraries
- C. Harrison Mann, Jr. Collection
  - Gray Commission - Correspondence. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Gray Commission - Correspondence. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Gray Commission - Printed Material. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Gray Commission - Printed Material. (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Gray Commission - Printed Material. (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Constitutional Revision Committee. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Constitutional Revision Committee. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Constitutional Revision Committee 1969 - Special Session. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Constitutional Revision Committee 1969 - Special Session. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Legislation Special Session 1969 - Misc. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - State Corp. Commission 1969 - Special Session. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Special Session 1969 - Correspondence. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers - Special Session 1969. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Political Info. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Political Info. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Bills, Journal from House of Delegates. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Senate Bills And joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Senate Bills And joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Senate Bills And joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Senate Bills And joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Senate Bills And joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Session 1968 House And Senate Documents. (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Session 1968 House And Senate Documents. (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Session 1968 House And Senate Documents. (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Session 1968 House And Senate Documents. (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - 3 Copies - Liberty Hill. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Books on No. Va, People and Land. (Box 47, Folder 2A)
  - Books on No. Va, People and Land. (Box 47, Folder 2B)
  - Contents Missing. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Appellate Justice in Va - 1970. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Democrat Publicity 1963 Folders. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Gray Commission. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Gray Commission. (Box 47, Folder 7A)
  - Gray Commission. (Box 47, Folder 7B)
  - Gray Commission. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Gray Commission. (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Gen. Assembly - Schools. (Box 47, Folder 10A)
  - Gen. Assembly - Schools. (Box 47, Folder 10B)
  - Publicity and Speech Material - Printed Elections. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Publicity and Speech Material - Printed Elections. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolution 1962. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolution 1962. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolution 1962. (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolution 1962. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolution 1962. (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolution 1962. (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolution 1962. (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 1 - 450. (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 1 - 450. (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 1 - 450. (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 1 - 450. (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 1 - 450. (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 1 - 450. (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 1 - 450. (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 450 - 1000. (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 450 - 1000. (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 450 - 1000. (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 450 - 1000. (Box 48B, Folder 23)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 450 - 1000. (Box 48B, Folder 24)
  - Sessions 1968 Senate and Joint Resolutions 450 - 1000. (Box 48B, Folder 25)
  - Senate and House Documents 1960. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Senate and House Documents 1960. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Senate and House Documents 1960. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Senate and House Documents 1960. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Senate and House Documents 1960. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Senate and House Documents 1960. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Senate and House Documents 1960. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Senate and House Documents. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Senate and House Documents 1966. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Senate and House Documents 1966. (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Senate and House Documents 1966. (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Senate and House Documents 1966. (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Documents 1954. (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Documents 1954. (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Documents 1954. (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Documents 1954. (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1964. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1964. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1964. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1964. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1964. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1964. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - House Bills and Joint Resolutions 1966. (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1966. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence 1971. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 1971. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - State Leg. and Va. Mag. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Catholics (Parochial Schools). (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - 1954, 1957, 1958. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - 1956. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - 1957. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - 1958. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - 1959. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Rough Copy. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Northern Virginia University Center 1952 - 53. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Council - 1953 - 54. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Council - 1955. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Educational Extension Services in Virginia 1954. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Board of Control 1961 - 67. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Minutes - Committee on Extension Services. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - C, Harrison Mann (Obits). (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Political Endorsements By Charles R. Fenwick, As Senator. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Slides from the C. Harrison Mann, Jr. Map Collection. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Original Pages 1- 50 (Rough Draft - Photocopy). (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Original Pages 1- 50 (Rough Draft - Photocopy). (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Final Copy of Pages 1- 32 (1 - 50). (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Final Copy and 1st Copy Pages 101- 138. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Final Copy and 1st Copy Pages 101- 138 (135 Typed). (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Original Copy and 1st Copy of Pages 200 - 247. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Final Copy of Pages 200 - 247. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Typed. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Acknowledgements, Footnotes, Inserts, Appendix, etc. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Dedication of the C. Harrison Mann Collection. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - GMU - Clippings - Rouse Book Store. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Mason Clippings 1958, 1961, 1972, New College (Mason) to be Built. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Mason Clippings - 1971, Arts and Science Building Dedicated. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - GMU Clippings 1975, Student Housing - Dorms. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - 1976, Mason Clippings - Law School. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Mason Clippings - 1977 - 1978, Dorms, Law School, Teacher Fired. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - GMU Clippings - 1967 New Buildings, GMU Birthday, Enrollment. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - GMU Clippings - VA, FFX Co. George Mason College 1968. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - GMU Clippings - 1969, Student Protesting, Funds given to Mason. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - GMU Clippings - 1970, Phys Ed. Complex, New Faculty. (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Mason Clippings 1973, 74, Law School. (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Comments on State Council of Higher Education GMU Law School Study by Lorin A. Thompson. (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - GMU Clippings 1963 GM College Plans. (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - GMU Clippings 1974 Law School, Bio Complex, Library Grant. (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - GMU Clippings 1962 Building College Started. (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - GMU Clippings 1964, 65, 66 George Mason College (Dedication Edition). (Box 58, Folder 16A)
  - GMU Clippings 1964, 65, 66 George Mason College (Dedication Edition). (Box 58, Folder 16B)
  - Obituaries (Copy of Early Letters @ UVA about No. VA. Branch). (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jackson Message Dec - 6th 1832. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Dec 8th 1832 Report of Secy. of War. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Dec 11, 1832 Jackson Proclamation. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Dec 13th 1832, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Dec 15th 1832, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Dec 22 1832 - N.Y on S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Dec 25th 1832, S.C. Nullification (Every Page). (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Dec 27th 1832, S.C. Nullification Page 3. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Dec 29th 1832, S.C. Nullification Page 2. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 1, 1833, S.C. Nullification Letter Page 3. (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 3, 1833, S.C. Nullification - The Common Law, Washington Proclamation Page 4. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 5, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 8, 1833, S.C. Nullification Legislature of MD Page 1. (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 19, 1833, S.C. Nullification (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 10, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 12, 1833, S.C. Nullification Page 2. (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 15, 1833, S.C. Nullification (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 17, 1833, S.C. Nullification (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 22, 1833, S.C. Nullification (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 24, 1833, S.C. Nullification (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 26, 1833, S.C. Nullification (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 29, 1833, S.C. Nullification (Box 59, Folder 21B)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Jan 31, 1833, S.C. Nullification (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 2, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 5, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 7, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 9, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 12, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 14, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 16, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 19, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 21, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 23, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 26, 1833, S.C. Nullification. (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb 28 1833. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 2 1833. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 5 1833. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 7 1833. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 23 1833. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 26 1833. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 28 1833. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 28 1833. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 28 1833. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 30 1833. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 02, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 04, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 06, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 09, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 11, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 13, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 16, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 18, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 20, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 23, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 25, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 27, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April, 30, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) May, 02, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) May, 04, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) May, 07, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) May, 09, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) May, 30, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) June, 20, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Dec, 12, 1833. (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Dec, 28, 1833 - The Oliver Branch. (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Dec, 31, 1833 - The Oliver Branch. (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb, 22, 1834 - Dvane, Secy. of Treas. #1. (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Feb, 27, 1834 - #2. (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 04, 1834 - Amer. Colonization Soc. #3. (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 04, 1834 - Amer. Colonization Soc. #4. (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April 19, 1834 - Calhoun P.1. (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April 26, 1834 - Leigh P.2. (Box 60, Folder 38)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) April 09, 1835 - Cincinnati - Gal. (Box 60, Folder 39)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Aug 12, 1835 - Riots in Baltimore. (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) Aug 29, 1835 - Slavery. (Box 60, Folder 41)
  - National Intelligencer (Washington) March 08, 1836 - Letter, John Tyler. (Box 60, Folder 42)
  - New York Daily Tribune (N.Y) April 29 1861 - Md. "Return of ____ in Balt." Gov. Hicks Message. (Box 60, Folder 43)
  - New York Daily Tribune (N.Y) May 07 1861 - VA Gov. Calls out troops. (Box 60, Folder 44)
  - New York Daily Tribune (N.Y) Jan. 03 1863 - Emancipation Proclamation. (Box 60, Folder 45)
  - Transportation - Mufflers. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Motor Vehicles. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Motor Vehicles. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Drunk Driving 1960 - Periodicals. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Drunk Driving 1959 - July. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Drunk Driving - Sept. 1959. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Drunk Driving Dec - 1959. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Correspondence. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Route 66. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Route 66. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Washington and Old Dominion RR. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Route 66 - Hearing - Mr. Owen. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Washington and Old Dominion R.R. - Mass Transit. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Washington and Old Dominion R.R. - Mass Transit. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Route 66 (1964). (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Shirley Highway 1961 - 63. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Shirley Highway. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Route 66. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Taxation - Correspondence - Re. Clippings, etc. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Taxation - Correspondence - Re. Clippings, etc. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - CHM- Research Materials. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - CHM - Newsclippings. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - CHM - Commission of Thomas Jefferson as Lieutenant of Albemarle. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - CHM - Gunston Hall. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - CHM - State Education. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - CHM - Published Materials. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - CHM - Notes on the Basket Edition of 1727. (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - CHM - Gunston Hall Exhibit. (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - CHM - Newspaper Articles. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - CHM - Notes on Maps Collected. (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Unity for Service National Exchange Club - Book of Golden Deeds. (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - CHM - Highways. (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Reply of Virginia Railroad Association to Reports of the Virginia Highway Users Association on Paragraphs (2) and (4) of Senate Joint Resolution No. 48. (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Brief of Virginia Highway Railway Association. (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Boston Daily Journal - April 19, 1861. (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Boston Daily Journal - Sept, 12, 1861. (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Boston Daily Journal - Aug. 30, 1814. (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Baltimore Daily Gazette May 14, 1863. (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - The New York Herald April 18, 1863. (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Illustration from inside General Atlas, 1782. (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Page from Atlas Nov, 1740. (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Map US - 1785 - Reprint. (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Map of Kent. (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - York Town Sesquicentennial Program. (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Map of Battlefield of Spotsylvania Courthouse. (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Speech by Hon, Rm T Hunter on the Subject of retrocession of Alexandria and Virginia, 1846. (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - George Washington's Maps of Mount Vernon 1793. (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Map of Northern Neck of Virginia 1737. (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Letters. (Box 65, Folder 29)